Hello, my name is Jay Desai. I'm a
chartered accountant and a content creator.
Today, in this video, I'm going to
tell you in a very simple way how you
can secure the future of yourself and your family.
In this video, I'll introduce you to
a simple product called
Tom & Jerry. Today, we'll understand four things.
Number one: what is term insurance and
why is it so important? Number two: when can
buying Tom & Jerry insurance
prove most beneficial for you? Number
three: what things should you especially keep in mind before buying it?
Number four:
how can you buy term insurance? Watch
this video till the end to know all this. So, let's
first look at term
insurance as a part of your
investment planning. According to me, term
insurance should be your first investment before you even start
thinking about
investing somewhere else.
I'm saying this
because family troubles can strike at any time.
In such situations, it's
very important to have a financial shield. Term
insurance is a solution that protects your
family from such troubles.  It provides timely
financial support. In these difficult times,
term insurance provides your family with a
large sum of money, which they can use to
fulfil their future goals in your absence
or repay a large loan.
Plus, term insurance is very affordable
and also helps in tax savings.
Now let's look at number two. When should you buy
term insurance? The
right time to buy term insurance is as soon as you
start investing. The earlier you buy term
insurance, the more you can earn
because when you are young, the premium
amount is very low. But if you
start investing in insurance today, to
know how much premium you will have to pay, you can check the
ICICI Term Insurance
Calculator link in this description. Now
coming to number three, let's talk about some important
things that you should consider
before investing. Number one: life cover. As a thumb rule, your
life cover should be 15 to 20 times your annual income.
Number two: claim settlement
ratio. This tells you about the number of
claims.  The insurance company has
settled the claim in a year. Therefore, it is important to
buy a term insurance plan from a brand
whose claim settlement
ratio is high and consistent so that you have the
assurance that your family's claim will be
settled. Number three: Riders: Riders are
like add-on benefits and can be
added to your term plan at a nominal cost. For example,
number one, if you
suffer from a critical illness like cancer, heart
disease, kidney disease, you get financial security for these. The
best part is
that you get the entire claim amount
without other hospital bills. Number two:
If you suffer from any physical disability due to any reason, the
company pays it
and ensures that you continue to
receive the policy benefits. Number three: If any
accident occurs, additional insurance is provided to your family in that case. The
next thing you must consider is the
brand. The most important thing
while buying term insurance is to go for one
of the trusted insurance partners
like ICICI Prudential Life, whose
stock is legacy.  Yes, and the financial banking of a big bank group.
Now coming to our
last point, you can
buy a term plan. There are two ways to buy a term plan. Either you
can contact your financial advisor or you can buy term insurance online.
These three easy steps: number one,
go to the ICICI Prudential Life website and calculate your premium. number two,
fill the application form. number three,
review the form and finally
complete the payment. And the date sheet is so simple, right?
Check out the term plans by
ICICI Prudential Life now by
clicking on the linking description below.
Because if the preparation is right, then victory is certain. This is by
contacting your financial advisor and
buying it online.